<resources>
    <string name="app_name">FirstWeekApp</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="open_res">open</string>
    <string name="close_res">open</string>
    <string name="restart_title">Restart</string>
    <string name="quit_title">Quit</string>
    <string name="music_title">Music</string>
    <string name="start_scene">start</string>
    <string name="marry_scene">marry</string>
    <string name="rightaway_scene_name">rightaway</string>
    <string name="game_scene_name">game</string>
    <string name="Sylvie_name">Sylvie</string>
    <string name="Me_name">Me</string>
    <string name="later_scene">later</string>
    <string name="book_scene_name">book</string>
    <string name="bad_end">Bad Ending</string>
    <string name="start1">It\'s only when I hear the sounds of shuffling feet and supplies being put away that I realize that the lecture\'s over.</string>
    <string name="start2">Professor Eileen\'s lectures are usually interesting, but today I just couldn\'t concentrate on it.</string>
    <string name="start3">I\'ve had a lot of other thoughts on my mind…thoughts that culminate in a question.</string>
    <string name="start4">It\'s a question that I\'ve been meaning to ask a certain someone.</string>
    <string name="later1">I can\'t get up the nerve to ask right now. With a gulp, I decide to ask her later.</string>
    <string name="later2">But I\'m an indecisive person.</string>
    <string name="later3">I couldn\'t ask her that day and I end up never being able to ask her.</string>
    <string name="later4">I guess I\'ll never know the answer to my question now…</string>
    <string name="rightaway1">Hi there! How was class?</string>
    <string name="rightaway2">Good</string>
    <string name="rightaway3">I can\'t bring myself to admit that it all went in one ear and out the other.</string>
    <string name="rightaway4">Hi there! How was class?</string>
    <string name="rightaway5">Are you going home now? Wanna walk back with me?</string>
    <string name="rightaway6">Sure!</string>
    <string name="rightaway7">After a short while, we reach the meadows just outside the neighborhood where we both live.</string>
    <string name="rightaway8">It\'s a scenic view I\'ve grown used to. Autumn is especially beautiful here.</string>
    <string name="rightaway9">When we were children, we played in these meadows a lot, so they\'re full of memories.</string>
    <string name="rightaway10">Hi there! How was class?</string>
    <string name="rightaway11">She turns to me and smiles. She looks so welcoming that I feel my nervousness melt away.</string>
    <string name="rightaway12">I\'ll ask her…!</string>
    <string name="rightaway13">Ummm… Will you…</string>
    <string name="rightaway14">Will you be my artist for a visual novel?</string>
    <string name="rightaway15">Silence.</string>
    <string name="rightaway16">She looks so shocked that I begin to fear the worst. But then…</string>
    <string name="rightaway17">Sure, but what\'s a visual novel?</string>
    <string name="rightaway18">It\'s a videogame.</string>
    <string name="rightaway19">It\'s an interactive book.</string>
    <string name="marry1">And so, we become a visual novel creating duo.</string>
    <string name="marry2">Over the years, we make lots of games and have a lot of fun making them.</string>
    <string name="marry3">We take turns coming up with stories and characters and support each other to make some great games!</string>
    <string name="marry4">And one day…</string>
    <string name="marry5">Hey…</string>
    <string name="marry6">Yes?</string>
    <string name="marry7">Will you marry me?</string>
    <string name="marry8">What? Where did this come from?</string>
    <string name="marry9">Come on, how long have we been dating?</string>
    <string name="marry10">A while…</string>
    <string name="marry11">These last few years we\'ve been making visual novels together, spending time together, helping each other…</string>
    <string name="marry12">I\'ve gotten to know you and care about you better than anyone else. And I think the same goes for you, right?</string>
    <string name="marry13">Sylvie…</string>
    <string name="marry14">But I know you\'re the indecisive type. If I held back, who knows when you\'d propose?</string>
    <string name="marry15">So will you marry me?</string>
    <string name="marry16">Of course I will! I\'ve actually been meaning to propose, honest!</string>
    <string name="marry17">I know, I know.</string>
    <string name="marry18">I guess… I was too worried about timing. I wanted to ask the right question at the right time.</string>
    <string name="marry19">You worry too much. If only this were a visual novel and I could pick an option to give you more courage!</string>
    <string name="marry20">We get married shortly after that.</string>
    <string name="marry21">Our visual novel duo lives on even after we\'re married…and I try my best to be more decisive.</string>
    <string name="marry22">Together, we live happily ever after even now</string>
    <string name="marry23">Good Ending.</string>
    <string name="start5">When we come out of the university, I spot her right away.</string>
    <string name="start6">I\'ve known Sylvie since we were kids. She\'s got a big heart and she\'s always been a good friend to me.</string>
    <string name="start7">But recently… I\'ve felt that I want something more.</string>
    <string name="start8">More than just talking, more than just walking home together when our classes end.</string>
    <string name="start10">To ask her right away.</string>
    <string name="start11">To ask her later.</string>
    <string name="game1">It\'s a kind of videogame you can play on your computer or a console.</string>
    <string name="game2">Visual novels tell a story with pictures and music.</string>
    <string name="game3">Sometimes, you also get to make choices that affect the outcome of the story.</string>
    <string name="game4">So it\'s like those choose-your-adventure books?</string>
    <string name="game5">Exactly! I\'ve got lots of different ideas that I think would work.</string>
    <string name="game6">It\'d be hard for me to make a visual novel alone.</string>
    <string name="game7">Well, sure! I can try. I just hope I don\'t disappoint you.</string>
    <string name="game8">You know you could never disappoint me, Sylvie.</string>
    <string name="book1">It\'s like an interactive book that you can read on a computer or a console.</string>
    <string name="book2">Interactive?</string>
    <string name="book3">You can make choices that lead to different events and endings in the story.</string>
    <string name="book4">So where does the \"visual\" part come in?</string>
    <string name="book5">Visual novels have pictures and even music, sound effects, and sometimes voice acting to go along with the text.</string>
    <string name="book6">I see! That certainly sounds like fun. I actually used to make webcomics way back when, so I\'ve got lots of story ideas.</string>
    <string name="book7">That\'s great! So…would you be interested in working with me as an artist?</string>
    <string name="book8">I\'d love to!</string>

</resources>